# **Asia Echols**

Maple Valley, WA asiabrieannelee@gmail.com - 9155409172

1.5 years experience in manufacturing production and machine operator. And 1 year receptionist experience

I am Able to handle multiple tasks on a daily basis, with ability to get them done efficiently. I take pride in time management and all areas of work, and always eager to learn more

WORK EXPERIENCE

### Operator 2/ line lead

Medline Industries - Hartland, WI -

August 2017 to September 2018

Started at Medline industries as a packager, and was instantly promoted to line lead operator 2 for the ability to learn fast, on all types of lines such as cosmetic bottle lines, medical tube lines and drug and device lines. This included hooking up tanks to the correct pipe lines, and bulk product, opening jobs, running the line, ensuing that labels dates, codes, fill height and weights were all correct and in spec.Employer reference: Janelle Kwarnocky Job title: manager/supervisor.Phone # 262-646- 0410Employer Reference: Sherry Taheri Job title: Production leadp>op>cbr>

# **Employee**

McDonald's - Pewaukee, WI -

August 2017 to October 2017

A crew member as a 2nd job

#### Receptionist

Seadrunar - Seattle, WA -

January 2017 to July 2017

Handled all incoming and outgoing calls, scheduling and reschedluong appointments. Answering qustions for customersEmployer refrenece: Tanner RacyPhone # 425 999 0669Personal refrence: Edith flores phone #206-883-3282

**EDUCATION** 

#### **GED**

# SKILLS

Assembly Line, Inspection

## ADDITIONAL INFORMATION

Great time management, and punctuality,Ability to handle tasks (multiple if needed) and complete fast and efficiently,Take pride in all aspects of work,Works well with all team members